const questions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a money laundering activity?",
    correct_answer:
      "Hiding your personal savings and income in a bank account.",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Handling the proceeds of crimes such as theft, fraud and tax evasion.",
      "being directly involved with any criminal or terrorist property.",
      "assisting in the laundering of any criminal or terrorist property",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is money laundering?",
    correct_answer:
      "Converting the proceeds of crime into assets that appear to have a legitimate origin",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Investing money in legal business",
      "Sending money to relatives outside the country.",
      "Washing money using water and domestic detergent.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which is the best course of action to take in case you suspect a customer is money laundering?",
    correct_answer:
      "Liaise with the logistics team to escalate to relevant authorities.",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Request suspect to include you in the activities.",
      "Investigate the suspect on your own.",
      "Keep quiet and hope they are not caught.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What do is the best course of action when you repeatedly receive gifts of considerable value from a dealer?",
    correct_answer: "Declare the gift to your organization lead/Logistics team",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Take the gift and thank the dealer.",
      "Accept the gift and donate to charity.",
      "Accept the gift and share with colleagues.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the definition of AML?",
    correct_answer: "Anti Money Laundering",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Anti Monetary Laundry",
      "Ante Money laundering",
      "Ante Money Laundry",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "How long should we take before reporting a suspicious AML activity?",
    correct_answer: "Report as soon as possible.",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Share with your colleague the juicy details before reporting",
      "Report after 14 days just to ensure your suspicions are correct",
      "Report when others have also reported.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a suspicious activity?",
    correct_answer:
      "A dealer requesting for the contacts of a regional manager.",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "A dealer requesting you to assist in undercutting.",
      "A dealer requesting you to store large undocumented sums of money in your safe/account.",
      "A dealer insisting on purchasing Safaricom products through your company as a third party.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is terrorism financing?",
    correct_answer:
      "When a person unlawfully and willfully provides or collects funds with the intention that these funds will be used in full or in part to carry out a terrorist act ",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Financing done by the ministry of tourism and internal affairs.",
      "Financing done by the ",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Why is money laundered by criminals?",
    correct_answer: "All of the above",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "To conceal or put some distance between themselves and the property",
      "To avoid detection of the underlying crimes",
      "To disguise the fact that the property comes from a crime",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is most prone to money laundering activities.",
    correct_answer: "All the answers provided",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Ministore operant",
      "Area Sales Manager",
      "Logistics team",
    ],
  },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the regional manager for Nairobi region?",
  //   correct_answer: "Mark Mosoti",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["Serah Gikaria", "Stella Misati", "Esther Kiaraho"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the regional manager for Coast region?",
  //   correct_answer: "Esther Kiaraho",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["Serah Gikaria", "Mark Mosoti", "Stella Misati"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the Safaricom Supply Chain HOD?",
  //   correct_answer: "Maryanne Karanja",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["Tom Mochama", "Francis Murabula", "Florence Kiburi"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the regional manager for Riftvalley region?",
  //   correct_answer: "Serah Gikaria",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["Esther Kiaraho", "Mark Mosoti", "Eugene Were"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the regional manager for central and North Eastern?",
  //   correct_answer: "Stella Misati",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["Esther Kiaraho", "Eugene Were", "Serah Gikaria"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "What does the abbreviation NPS in customer service mean?",
  //   correct_answer: "Net Promoter score",
  //   incorrect_answers: [
  //     "National Police service",
  //     "Net Professional Service",
  //     "Net Prism of Success",
  //   ],
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the current Safaricom CEO?",
  //   correct_answer: "Peter Ndegwa",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["Sylvia Mulinge", "Michael Joseph", "Bob Collymore"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "How do you tell a staff is authorized to collect stocks at the ministores",
  //   correct_answer:
  //     "We use the portal to identify the staff details and their current status.",
  //   incorrect_answers: [
  //     "By face and name since they usually collect stocks for a particular dealer.",
  //     "Through an email authorization letter sent by the distribution team.",
  //     "All of the above.",
  //   ],
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "When a dealer nominates staff in the portal, how long does it take to reflect in your ministore",
  //   correct_answer: "Less than a minute",
  //   incorrect_answers: ["1 hour", "2 hours", "24 hours"],
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "In picklist nomination in the dealer portal, which class of staff does not qualify to be issued with stock?",
  //   correct_answer: "Retired Staff",
  //   incorrect_answers: [
  //     "Approved staff",
  //     "A staff with a passport as an identification document.",
  //     "An MPESA agent staff",
  //   ],
  // },
]
export default questions
